<article_content id="A9127">
    <para id="A9127P126972">
        <sent id="A9127P126972S210390">
            <![CDATA[Once when I was six years old I saw a magnificent picture in a book, called True Stories from Nature, about the primeval forest.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126972S210393">
            <![CDATA[It was a picture of a boa constrictor in the act of swallowing an animal.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126972S210396"><![CDATA[Here is a copy of the drawing.]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P126978">
        <img>
            <url>https://static.baydn.com/read/media_store/ed34de4548f2114db5ebd997c07e10b4.jpg
            </url>
            <width>301</width>
            <height>183</height>
        </img>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P126984">
        <sent id="A9127P126984S4127745">
            <![CDATA[In the book it said: "Boa constrictors swallow their prey whole, without chewing it.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126984S4127748">
            <![CDATA[After that they are not able to move, and they sleep through the six months that they need for digestion."]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P126990">
        <sent id="A9127P126990S210411">
            <![CDATA[I pondered deeply, then, over the adventures of the jungle.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126990S210414">
            <![CDATA[And after some work with a colored pencil I succeeded in making my first drawing.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126990S210417"><![CDATA[My Drawing Number One.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P126990S210420"><![CDATA[It looked something like this:]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P126993">
        <img>
            <url>https://static.baydn.com/read/media_store/8b8d88e2c6133b5ed0d8926730e56a7d.jpg
            </url>
            <width>241</width>
            <height>80</height>
        </img>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P126996">
        <sent id="A9127P126996S210426">
            <![CDATA[I showed my masterpiece to the grown-ups, and asked them whether the drawing frightened them.]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127002">
        <sent id="A9127P127002S4127751"><![CDATA[But they answered: "Frighten?]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127002S4127754">
            <![CDATA[Why should anyone be frightened by a hat?"]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127008">
        <sent id="A9127P127008S210438"><![CDATA[My drawing was not a picture of a hat.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127008S210441">
            <![CDATA[It was a picture of a boa constrictor digesting an elephant.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127008S210444">
            <![CDATA[But since the grown-ups were not able to understand it, I made another drawing: I drew the inside of a boa constrictor, so that the grown-ups could see it clearly.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127008S210447"><![CDATA[They always need to have things explained.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127008S210450"><![CDATA[My Drawing Number Two looked like this:]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127011">
        <img>
            <url>https://static.baydn.com/read/media_store/fd6b201a8f5c184c2fb33d5b6b26bf69.jpg
            </url>
            <width>242</width>
            <height>92</height>
        </img>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127017">
        <sent id="A9127P127017S210456">
            <![CDATA[The grown-ups' response, this time, was to advise me to lay aside my drawings of boa constrictors, whether from the inside or the outside, and devote myself instead to geography, history, arithmetic, and grammar.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127017S210459">
            <![CDATA[That is why, at the age of six, I gave up what might have been a magnificent career as a painter.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127017S210462">
            <![CDATA[I had been disheartened by the failure of my Drawing Number One and my Drawing Number Two.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127017S210465">
            <![CDATA[Grown-ups never understand anything by themselves, and it is tiresome for children to be always and forever explaining things to them.]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127023">
        <sent id="A9127P127023S210468">
            <![CDATA[So then I chose another profession, and learned to pilot airplanes.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127023S210471">
            <![CDATA[I have flown a little over all parts of the world; and it is true that geography has been very useful to me.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127023S210474">
            <![CDATA[At a glance I can distinguish China from Arizona.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127023S210477">
            <![CDATA[If one gets lost in the night, such knowledge is valuable.]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127029">
        <sent id="A9127P127029S210480">
            <![CDATA[In the course of this life I have had a great many encounters with a great many people who have been concerned with matters of consequence.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127029S210483"><![CDATA[I have lived a great deal among grown-ups.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127029S210486">
            <![CDATA[I have seen them intimately, close at hand.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127029S210489">
            <![CDATA[And that hasn't much improved my opinion of them.]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127035">
        <sent id="A9127P127035S210492">
            <![CDATA[Whenever I met one of them who seemed to me at all clear-sighted, I tried the experiment of showing him my Drawing Number One, which I have always kept.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127035S210495">
            <![CDATA[I would try to find out, so, if this was a person of true understanding.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127035S210498">
            <![CDATA[But, whoever it was, he, or she, would always say:]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127041">
        <sent id="A9127P127041S4127757"><![CDATA["That is a hat."]]></sent>
    </para>
    <para id="A9127P127050">
        <sent id="A9127P127050S210507">
            <![CDATA[Then I would never talk to that person about boa constrictors, or primeval forests, or stars.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127050S210510"><![CDATA[I would bring myself down to his level.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127050S210513">
            <![CDATA[I would talk to him about bridge, and golf, and politics, and neckties.]]></sent>
        <sent id="A9127P127050S210516">
            <![CDATA[And the grown-up would be greatly pleased to have met such a sensible man.]]></sent>
    </para>
</article_content>